module.exports =
{
    EN_US:
    {
       SUBJECT_PRONOUNS:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['It is in the garden.','They is in the garden.','I is in the garden.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['She is from Italy.','I is from Italy.','They is from Italy.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['It is big.','He speak Russian.','You is big.',],
            }
        ],
        TOBE_AFIRMATIVE:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['You are French.','You is French.','French you are.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['This cheese is from Ireland.','From Ireland this cheese is.','Is Ireland from this cheese.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['She\'s 14 years old.','She\'re 14 years old.','She\'ve 14 year old.',],
            }
        ],
        TOBE_NEGATIVE:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['We aren\'t from Malta.','We havn\'t from Malta.','We amn\'t from Malta.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['You are not old.','You not are old.','You am not old.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['I am not a writer.','Not I am a writer.','A writer I am not.',],
            }
        ],
        TOBE_INTEROCATIVE:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['Is she a doctor?','Are she a doctor?','She is a doctor?',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['Are we tall?','Are he tall?','We are tall?',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['Are you happy?','Am you happy?','Is you happy?',],
            }
        ],
        CARDINAL_NUMBERS:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['She eats two bananas every day.','She eats tu bananas every day.','She eats too bananas every day.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['I have one apple in my bag.','I have on apple in my bag.','I have apple one in my bag.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
                answers: ['The days of the week are seven.','The days of the week are four.','The days of the week are six.',],
            }
        ]
    },
    ES_ES:
    {
        SUBJECT_PRONOUNS:
        [
            {
              id:'0',
              question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
              answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">It is in the garden</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">They is in the garden</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">I is in the garden</lang>.',],
            },
            {
              id:'1',
              question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
              answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">She is from Italy</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">I is from Italy</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">They is from Italy</lang>.',],
            },
            {
              id:'2',
              question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
              answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">It is big</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">I is big</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">He speak Russian</lang>.',],
            }
        ],
        TOBE_AFIRMATIVE:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">You are French</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">You is French</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">French you are</lang>.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">This cheese is from Ireland</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">From Ireland this cheese is</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">Is Ireland from this cheese</lang>.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">She\'s 14 years old</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">She\'re 14 years old</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">She\'ve 14 year old</lang>.',],
            }
        ],
        TOBE_NEGATIVE:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">We aren\'t from Malta</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">We havn\'t from Malta</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">We amn\'t from Malta</lang>.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">You are not old</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">You not are old</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">You am not old</lang>.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">I am not a writer</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">Not I am a writer</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">A writer I am not</lang>.',],
            }
        ],
        TOBE_INTEROCATIVE:
        [
           {
                id:'0',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">Is she a doctor?</lang>','<lang xml:lang="en-US">Are she a doctor?</lang>','<lang xml:lang="en-US">She is a doctor?</lang>',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">Are we tall?</lang>','<lang xml:lang="en-US">Are he tall?</lang>','<lang xml:lang="en-US">We are tall?</lang>',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">Are you happy?</lang>','<lang xml:lang="en-US">Am you happy?</lang>','<lang xml:lang="en-US">Is you happy?</lang>',],
            }
        ],
        CARDINAL_NUMBERS:
        [
            {
                id:'0',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">She eats two bananas every day</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">She eats tu bananas every day</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">She eats too bananas every day</lang>.',],
            },
            {
                id:'1',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">I have one apple in my bag</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">I have on apple in my bag</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">I have apple one in my bag</lang>.',],
            },
            {
                id:'2',
                question: '¿Cúal es la frase correcta?',
                answers: ['<lang xml:lang="en-US">The days of the week are seven</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">The days of the week are four</lang>.','<lang xml:lang="en-US">The days of the week are six</lang>.',],
            }
        ]
    }
}
